<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<index version="1" name="Saike Tools" commit="2c915baa08da59f79573dbbcf1f717ed3422271b">
  <category name="SpectrumAnalyzer">
    <reapack name="LoadSpectrum.lua" type="script" desc="Multi-channel spectral analyzer.">
      <metadata>
        <description><![CDATA[{\rtf1\ansi\deff0{\fonttbl{\f0 \fswiss Helvetica;}{\f1 Courier;}}
{\colortbl;\red255\green0\blue0;\red0\green0\blue255;}
\widowctrl\hyphauto

{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs28 Multi-Channel Spectral Analyzer\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 This script opens a JSFX multispectrum analyzer on a new FX track. It is basically an extensively modified version of the spectral analyzer shipped with reaper. Calling the script will automatically route up to 16 channels to this FX and open the spectral analysis window.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs28 White/Black\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 Chooses background color.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs28 Smoothing\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 Chooses size of spectral smoothing. Spectral smoothing is performed in the frequency domain, using larger smoothing for higher values. Note that this is not an unbiased smoother. More smoothing means that peaks get wider and the spectrum becomes less accurate. The noise is also suppressed however, which makes it easier to read when there are multiple spectra.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs28 Color map\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 Specifies colormap for spectral analyzer.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs28 Scale\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 Scale indicators the zoom factor on the spectrum analyzer.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs28 Integrate\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 Integrate spectrum over time. This makes the spectrum less noisy, but less sensitive to short transients. Smoothness is a tradeoff between smoothing (width), integration time (transients) and noise (no smoothing or integration time).\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs28 Floor\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 Specify where to put the noise floor.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs28 Window\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 Window function. Defaults to Blackman-Harris for its resolution.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs28 FFT\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 FFT window size. 8192 is pretty good. Higher is heavier on the CPU.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs28 Log(Sonogram)\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 Enabling this shows the sonogram with a logarithmic frequency axis. Disabling it means linear.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs28 Sonogram/Time toggle\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 Determine whether you want to see the waveform or the sonogram. Waveform is good for studying transients. Sonogram is good for studying frequencies over time.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs32 Channel buttons\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 The next buttons indicate what channels are visualized. Enabling or disabling them can be done by clicking them with the left mouse button. Clicking them with the right mouse button will make them the active channel in the sonogram or time window. This way, you can study the sonograms of the channels separately.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs28 Sum\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 Indicates the sum of the signal. This will show the left and right channel in black and grey in the main graph. Enabling or disabling can be done by left clicking. Clicking this with the outer mouse button will show the signal in the sonogram or time window.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs28 Ch1 - Ch16\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 The channels that are routed to the spectral analyser. Enabling or disabling can be done by left clicking. Clicking this with the outer mouse button will show the signal in the sonogram or time window.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs32 Sonogram mode:\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 Double-clicking the sonogram will toggle its size. Clicking and dragging with the left mouse button will change how bright it is. Clicking with the right mouse button will switch colormap. The channel you're viewing and the scale are shown on the top left. The colormap on the bottom left. Switch with outer mouse button on the channel button in the second row on the top. Mousewheel will change the scaling w.r.t. the frequency axis. Doubleclicking alters the sonogram size.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs32 Time mode:\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 Clicking and dragging or using the mouse wheel will change the scale of the graph. The channel you're viewing is shown on the top left. Switch with outer mouse button on the channel button in the second row on the top. Doubleclicking alters the signal window size.\par}
}
]]></description>
        <link rel="website">https://github.com/JoepVanlier/JSFX</link>
      </metadata>
      <version name="0.1" author=": Joep Vanlier" time="2018-05-08T20:42:31Z">
        <source main="main">https://github.com/JoepVanlier/JSFX/raw/6916597e9c56b069929ca4eded16bbaeb82bb91b/SpectrumAnalyzer/LoadSpectrum.lua</source>
        <source file="SaikeMultiSpectroMeter.jsfx">https://github.com/JoepVanlier/JSFX/raw/6916597e9c56b069929ca4eded16bbaeb82bb91b/SpectrumAnalyzer/SaikeMultiSpectroMeter.jsfx</source>
      </version>
    </reapack>
    <reapack name="StereoManipulator.jsfx" type="effect" desc="Saike Stereo Manipulator">
      <version name="1.0" author="Sai'ke" time="2018-05-08T20:29:14Z">
        <changelog><![CDATA[init]]></changelog>
        <source>https://github.com/JoepVanlier/JSFX/raw/0eeb6f249e4c48143bd75a3db4c2317ee41152da/SpectrumAnalyzer/StereoManipulator.jsfx</source>
      </version>
    </reapack>
    <reapack name="StereoSpectrumSplit.jsfx" type="effect" desc="Saike Stereo Spectrum">
      <version name="1.0" author="Cockos, Joep Vanlier" time="2018-05-08T20:29:14Z">
        <changelog><![CDATA[init]]></changelog>
        <source>https://github.com/JoepVanlier/JSFX/raw/0eeb6f249e4c48143bd75a3db4c2317ee41152da/SpectrumAnalyzer/StereoSpectrumSplit.jsfx</source>
      </version>
    </reapack>
  </category>
</index>
